David Luce

Web & Software Engineer

Bountiful, UT dluce14@gmail.com 8019910135

Exceptional and dependable web developer with a strong work ethic. Well-versed in HTML, CSS, Javascript. A believer in constant progression, that life is the greatest teacher. Knowledgeable in a variety of computer languages as well as the principles and techniques of website construction and maintenance. Broadening horizons to keep up with current market trends, evolving business models and newer technologies. 1-2 years' experience and on the job self-learning creating e-commerce websites to meet guidelines for merchant applications. Set up and led an extensive corporate training initiative, growing the company from 30 employees to several hundred. Certified in Full Stack Web Development from University of Utah. Excited to create new content and technologies for users enjoyment.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Software Engineer

Ivinex - Bountiful, UT August 2019 to September 2019

Short internship building custom components for business CRMs with PHP and Vanilla Javascript.

Jr. Developer

Nutra Drop, LLC - West Jordan, UT June 2018 to June 2019

Assisted a team with building 100+ responsive websites for online eCommerce stores. Using a variety of programs and softwares that included Bootstrap 4, HTML, CSS, minimal Laravel PHP, Wordpress, Cloudflare and online hosting platforms.

Sales Manger

Direct Business Lending - Sandy, UT November 2013 to May 2017

Managed 30+ sales agents, helping company exceed target sales goals. Other responsibilities included provisioning of phones, integration and training of new software, onboarding and payroll.

Education

Certification Course in Full Stack Web Development

University of Utah - Salt Lake City, UT May 2019 to Present

Enrolled in AS - Computer Science

Salt Lake Community College - Taylorsville, UT Present

AS - Some College Credit in General Studies

Weber State University - Ogden, UT 2015 to 2017

High school or equivalent

Bountiful High School - Bountiful, UT 2002 to 2005

Skills

Git (2 years), Javascript (Less than 1 year), MYSQL (Less than 1 year), CSS (1 year), HTML 5 (2 years), MongoDB (Less than 1 year), Bootstrap (2 years), ReactJS (Less than 1 year), JQuery (Less than 1 year), Node.js (Less than 1 year), Heroku Database (Less than 1 year), My (Less than 1 year), Front-End, Express.js (Less than 1 year)

Links

https://github.com/Droptime24

https://www.linkedin.com/in/luce-david/